Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
Ernest Lundeen Papers,
1860-1944
50003
Lundeen, Ernest, 1878-1940
384 manuscript boxes, 7 card file boxes, 2 oversize boxes, 1 cubic foot box, 42 envelopes, 2 albums (156.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, notes, clippings, printed matter, and photographs, relating to American politics, American neutrality in World Wars I and II, military conscription in the United States, New Deal social and economic legislation, the Supreme Court controversy of 1937, the Progressive movement in the United States, and the Minnesota Farmer-Labor Party.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1950.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Farmer-Labor Party (Minn.); United States. Congress; United States. Supreme Court; Draft--United States; Progressivism (United States politics); World War, 1914-1918; World War, 1914-1918--United States; World War, 1939-1945; World War, 1939-1945--United States; Minnesota--Politics and government; United States--Economic policy--1933-1945; United States--Neutrality; United States--Politics and government--20th century; United States--Politics and government; United States--Foreign relations; Statesmen--United States
Biographical Note
1878 August 4 Born near Beresford, South Dakota
1898 Joined the Minnesota National Guard
1901 BA degree, Carleton College
1906 Admitted to the bar
1910-1914 Member, Minnesota House of Representatives
1917-1919, 1933-1937 Member, U.S. House of Representatives
1919 Married Norma Matheson Ward
1920-1922 Editor and publisher of Uncle Sam
1937-1940 Member, U.S. Senate
1939 Formed the Make Europe Pay War Debts Committee
1940 August 31 Died near Lovettsville, Virginia
Series Description
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1894-1942. (Boxes 1-218)
  Family, business, personal, congressional, and constituent correspondence arranged first chronologically, then alphabetically either by last name of correspondent or by initial of name of company or institution, and occasionally by subject matter or physical form. General correspondence is in Boxes 1-61, 70, and 166-218; correspondence and reference files about federal and state agencies are in Boxes 71-72; and constituent mail is in Boxes 62-69, 73-89 (includes some correspondence with clients and friends), 90-94 (re conscription during World War I), 95-101 (re U.S. Supreme Court), 102-139, 140-162 (re conscription during World War II, U.S. neutrality, and repeal of the 1937 embargo to discourage sale of arms to Spain during the Spanish Civil War), and 163-165
- SUBJECT FILE, 1906-1942. (Boxes 219-302)
  Notes, memoranda, pamphlets, clippings, correspondence, newsletters, articles, maps, charts, reports arranged alphabetically by subject. This file postdates Senator Lundeen's death because Mrs. Lundeen added material to various subjects
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1894-1944. (Boxes 303-321)
  Biographies, family genealogies, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, lists, memberships, reports, schedules, clippings, other printed matter arranged alphabetically by subject or physical form. Some files about Mrs. Lundeen are included
- CAMPAIGN FILE, 1906-1940. (Boxes 322-339)
  Campaign literature, clippings, research materials, speeches, and correspondence describing candidates and issues in local or national elections. Arranged first chronologically, then by physical form
- CONGRESSIONAL FILE, 1916-1940. (Boxes 340-348)
  Memoranda, reports, office finances and personnel, minutes, pamphlets, press releases, itineraries, calls to committee meetings, clippings and miscellany arranged alphabetically by subject
- LAW OFFICE FILE, 1906-1914. (Boxes 349-353)
  Office docket, legal documents, financial records and correspondence arranged alphabetically by physical form
- LEGISLATION, 1910-1940. (Boxes 354-369)
  Research materials, drafts and printed copies of bills and correspondence arranged chronologically
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1892-1940. (Boxes 370-384)
  Drafts and printed copies of speeches, debates, articles, notes and background materials arranged chronologically
- CARD FILE, n.d. (Boxes 385-391)
  Index cards of names of campaign workers, political supporters and non-supporters filed alphabetically and miscellaneous files unsorted
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1916-1940. (Boxes 392-393)
  Political campaign broadsides, an election certificate, clipping scrapbooks, a poem, and a tribute to Lundeen
- MISCELLANY, n.d. (Box 394)
  Checkbooks, check stubs, bank statements, bills and receipts
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1860-1940. (Photo file)
  1363 prints, 58 post cards and 2 albums depicting Ernest Lundeen and others including family members, friends, political colleagues, and views of Hawaii and the Soviet Union
Container List
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1894-1942
  * The headings used throughout are those established by Ernest Lundeen 1894-1928.
  - 1894-1928. Correspondence with family and friends arranged alphabetically
    - A unsorted (Box 1., Folder 1)
    - Almen, John A. (Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Anna B. (Folder 3)
    - Anderson, G. R. (Folder 4)
    - Anderson, H. C. (Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Sydney (Folder 6)
    - Anderson, W. M. (Folder 7)
    - Anderson and Gleason (Folder 8)
    - B unsorted (Folder 9)
    - Baneret Publishing Company (Folder 10)
    - Barkman, Carl (Folder 11)
    - Baumgart, E. G. (Folder 12)
    - Bell, David C. (Folder 13)
    - Benedict, C. B. (Folder 14)
    - Boutell Brothers (Folder 15)
    - Braasch, W. F. (Folder 16)
    - Bradshaw Brothers (Folder 17)
    - Burkheimer, Fanny (Folder 18)
    - Burnquist, J. A. A. (Folder 19)
    - C unsorted (Folder 20)
    - Carleton College (Folder 21)
    - Caton, T. J. (Folder 22)
    - Chase, Ray (Folder 23)
    - Crume, George P. (Folder 24)
    - D unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Dayton High School, Dayton, Iowa (Folder 26)
    - Dunwoody, Emma J. (Folder 27)
    - E unsorted (Folder 28)
    - Grand Army of the Republic
      - General (Folder 29)
      - Pensions (Folder 30)
    - H, I unsorted (Folder 31)
    - Iowa debate, 1903 (Folder 32)
    - J unsorted (Folder 33)
    - Johnson, C. E. (Folder 34)
    - Johnson, Carl J. (Folder 35)
    - Johnson, George E. Q. (Folder 36)
    - Johnson, J. Fred (Folder 37)
    - Johnson, Nimrod A. (Folder 38)
    - Jones, Stiles P. (Folder 39)
    - Jorgenson, John F. (Folder 40)
    - Justice, Department of (Folder 41)
    - K unsorted (Box 2., Folder 1-2)
    - Kaplan, Seeman (Folder 3)
    - Kauffman, C. S. (Folder 4)
    - Kaveny, M. (Folder 5)
    - Keating, Edward (Folder 6)
    - Kelly, J. R. (Folder 7)
    - Kinsell, Leonard (Folder 8)
    - Klein, Frank (Folder 9)
    - Kleinmann, Charles P. (Folder 10)
    - Knapp, Charles F. (Folder 11)
    - Knudson, Knutson (s) (Folder 12)
    - Knutson, Harold (Folder 13)
    - Koch, Hugo V. (Folder 14)
    - Koschel, Gustave (Folder 15)
    - Kruger, Henry (Folder 16)
    - L unsorted (Folder 17-18)
    - Labor, Department of (Folder 19)
    - Lafans, Arthur R. (Folder 20)
    - La Follette, Robert (Folder 21)
    - Lagergren, Elizabeth (Lizzie) Lundeen (Folder 22)
    - Lang, James (Folder 23)
    - Larson, Harry (Folder 24)
    - Lawrence, William (Folder 25)
    - Laybourn, Charles G. (Folder 26)
    - Layman, Martin G. (Folder 27)
    - Lee, E. T. (Folder 28)
    - Lidman, H. E. (Folder 29)
    - Lincoln, Fred S. (Folder 30)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A., Sr. (Box 3., Folder 1)
    - Linden, Gertrude (Folder 2)
    - Linden, Philip T. (Folder 3)
    - Lindholm, A. G. (Folder 4)
    - Little, E. C. (Folder 5)
    - Lundeen's letters to family members (Folder 6)
    - M unsorted (Folder 7)
    - Marbury, Elizabeth (Folder 8)
    - Meidell, H. J. (Folder 9)
    - Mexican service, Regiment for (Folder 10)
    - Moe, Christian (Folder 11)
    - N unsorted (Folder 12)
    - Naslund, Abraham (Folder 13)
    - O unsorted (Folder 14)
    - P unsorted (Folder 15)
    - R unsorted (Folder 16)
    - S unsorted (Folder 17-19)
    - Samuels, Anna Lundeen (Folder 20)
    - T unsorted (Folder 21)
    - Townsend, C. (Folder 22)
    - Tracy, G. H. (Folder 23)
    - V unsorted (Folder 24)
    - W unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Wassgren, C. S. (Folder 26)
    - Widen, Esther Lundeen (Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Woodrow (Folder 28)
    - World War Veterans Auxiliary (Folder 29)
    - Wright, Franklin R. (Folder 30)
    - Y unsorted (Folder 31)
    - Young, James (Folder 32)
  - 1906-1932. Correspondence with organizations; speech invitations, some personal financial records, arranged alphabetically
    - A - Books (Box 4., Folder 1-30)
    - America First Committee (Folder 4-5)
    - American Club of Minneapolis (Folder 6-8)
    - M. Sigbert Awes Company (Folder 23)
    - British - Cooperative (Box 5., Folder 1-30)
    - Campaign 1912 (Folder 7)
    - Campaign 1920 (Folder 8)
    - Campaign 1922 (Folder 9)
    - Carleton College (Folder 10)
    - Countryman - Finnish (Box 6., Folder 1-36)
    - Delta Sigma Rho (Folder 19)
    - Ford's - Harding (Box 7., Folder 1-28)
    - Harcourt, Iowa (Folder 27)
    - Hawaii, 1917 - Lansing (Box 8., Folder 1-29)
    - Income tax, 1912-1918 (Folder 6)
    - Jayne, Trafford N. (Folder 14)
    - La Follette, Robert (Folder 27)
    - Legislation - Mason (Box 9., Folder 1-24)
    - Linden, Philip (Folder 6)
    - Lundeen, David (Folder 9)
    - Lundeen for Governor (Folder 11)
    - Lundeen family (Folder 12)
    - Lundeen, Joel (Folder 14)
    - Masonic - Moe (Box 10., Folder 1-15)
    - Memorial Day speeches, 1919-1922 (Folder 3-7)
    - Minnesota National Guard, Company F (Folder 14)
    - Moe, Henry (Folder 15)
    - Moline - Official (Box 11., Folder 1-41)
    - Ogallala - Receipts (Box 12., Folder 1-30)
    - Ortonville (Folder 2)
    - People's Council of America (Folder 9)
    - Rankin, Jeannette (Folder 28)
    - Red Wing, Minnesota - Standard Press (Box 13., Folder 1-27)
    - Republican caucuses, 1917-1918 (Folder 3)
    - Shooting file (personal sports activity) (Folder 17)
    - Spanish War veterans (Folder 24)
    - Statements - Walthill, Nebraska (Box 14., Folder 1-43)
    - U.S. Congress, 1919, Russian resolution by Lundeen (Folder 28)
    - University of Minnesota (Folder 29)
    - Viereck's The American Weekly (Folder 37)
    - War - Woman Suffrage Association (Box 15., Folder 1-28)
  - 1930-1932. Correspondence filed alphabetically by subject, organization and individuals
    - A - B (Box 16., Folder 1)
    - C - D (Folder 2)
    - Dayton, Iowa speech, 1932 May 30 (Folder 3)
    - E - G (Folder 4)
    - H - J (Folder 5)
    - K (Folder 6)
    - L (Box 17., Folder 1)
    - Lawson, Victor E. (Folder 2)
    - League for Independent Political Action (Folder 3)
    - League of Nations (Folder 4)
    - League of Women Voters (Folder 5)
    - Lowson, Frank (Folder 6)
    - Lundeen, family (Folder 7)
    - M (Folder 8)
    - N - Q (Folder 9)
    - Olson, Floyd B. (Folder 10)
    - R (Box 18., Folder 1)
    - S (Folder 2)
    - Sandgren, Ehard (Folder 3)
    - T - Z (Folder 4)
  - 1933-1935. A chronological continuation of the previous series
    - A - Aviation (Box 19., Folder 1-22)
    - B - Bilbo (Box 20., Folder 1-14)
    - Binderup - Civic and Commerce Association (Box 21., Folder 1-29)
    - Bonus Expeditionary Force (Folder 7-8)
    - Camp Riley (Folder 15)
    - Campaign 1934 (Folder 16)
    - Civil Service Commission - Consumers Cooperative (Box 22., Folder 1-21)
    - Copyright bill - Economy bill repeal (Box 23., Folder 1-17)
    - Dehnel, Paul (Folder 5)
    - Delta Sigma Rho (Folder 6)
    - Economy legislation - Farm Credit Administration (Box 24., Folder 1-19)
    - Farm legislation - Farmers Holiday Association (Box 25., Folder 1-24)
    - Farmer Labor Association (Folder 4-20)
    - Farmers National Grain Corporation - Flood Control (Box 26., Folder 1-33)
    - Federal employees (Folder 6-18)
    - Folding room - Gillilland, Lillian (Box 27., Folder 1-18)
    - Gillilland, Lillian - Gray, Finley H. (Box 28., Folder 1-18)
    - Gross - Home Owners Loan Corporation, A-C (Box 29., Folder 1-22)
    - Home Owners Loan Corporation, D-J - Indians (Box 30., Folder 1-21)
    - Indians - L unsorted (Box 31., Folder 1-32)
    - Johnson, Magnus (Folder 20)
    - Koch, Hugo V. (Folder 27)
    - Kvale, Paul (Folder 31)
    - L unsorted - Legislative, District of Columbia (Box 32., Folder 1-18)
    - Labor, Department of (Folder 3)
    - Legislative, Economy - Lussnig, Michael (Box 33., Folder 1-17)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A., Sr. (Folder 5)
    - Linden, Philip T. (Folder 6)
    - Lundeen bill, H. R. 2827 (Folder 8)
    - Lundeen bill, H. R. 7598 (Folder 9)
    - Lundeen, David (Folder 10)
    - Lundeen, Ernest (Folder 11)
    - Lundeen, Ernest Ward (Folder 12)
    - Lundeen, Joan (Folder 13)
    - Lundeen, Joel (Folder 14)
    - Lundeen, Norma Ward (Folder 15)
    - M unsorted - Minneapolis Building Trades Council (Box 34., Folder 1-25)
    - Marsh, Benjamin C. (Folder 11)
    - Minneapolis Central Labor Union - National Dairy Union (Box 35., Folder 1-25)
    - Moe, Henry (Folder 16)
    - Mudge, Rollo (Folder 19)
    - National Education Association - Navy, U.S. (Box 36., Folder 1-20)
    - National Recovery Administration (Folder 8-12)
    - Newspaper list - Petitions introduced, 74th Congress (Box 37., Folder 1-20)
    - Olson, Floyd B. (Folder 10)
    - Petitions introduced, 73rd Congress - Press releases (Box 38., Folder 1-22)
    - Printing - Redistricting (Box 39., Folder 1-23)
    - Ramee, Per (Folder 17)
    - Rankin, Jeannette (Folder 18)
    - Reforestation Act - Shipping (Box 40., Folder 1-40)
    - Rost, Ernest C. (Folder 12)
    - Russian Railway Service Corps (Folder 15)
    - Shrine convention - Stillwater Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 41., Folder 1-40)
    - Social insurance (Folder 10-19)
    - Stock Exchange - Treasury Department (Box 42., Folder 1-20)
    - Treasury check to Lundeen for service-related disability (Folder 19)
    - U unsorted - Veterans legistation (Box 43., Folder 1-16)
    - United Spanish War Veterans (Folder 4-7)
    - Van Kleeck, Mary (Folder 10)
    - Veterans National Rank and File Committee - Wise, F. A. (Box 44., Folder 1-27)
    - W.D.G.Y. radio station (Folder 12)
    - W unsorted - Zink, E. H. (Box 45., Folder 1-15)
    - Widen, Ed and Esther Lundeen (Folder 3)
    - Wilkins, Anna Lundeen (Folder 4)
  - 1936. A chronological continuation of the previous series (Folder 46.)
    - A unsorted - Boy Scouts (Folder 1-19)
    - C unsorted - Campaign 1936 (Box 47., Folder 1-4)
    - Campaign 1936 - E unsorted (Box 48., Folder 1-20)
    - F unsorted - Government Printing Office (Box 49., Folder 1-30)
    - Farmer Labor Association (Folder 4-14)
    - Gillilland, Lillian (Folder 28)
    - H unsorted - L unsorted (Box 50., Folder 1-15)
    - L unsorted - Lundeen family (Box 51., Folder 1-14)
    - M unsorted - National Emergency Council (Box 52., Folder 1-22)
    - National Grange - Puerto Rico (Box 53., Folder 1-25)
    - Olson, Floyd B. (Folder 9)
    - Q unsorted - St. Thomas Military Academy (Box 54., Folder 1-17)
    - Saturday Lunch Club - Veterans Administration (Box 55., Folder 1-27)
    - Van Kleeck, Mary (Folder 26)
    - W unsorted - Y-Z unsorted (Box 56., Folder 1-5)
  - 1937-1940. A chronological continuation of the previous series
    - A unsorted - Employment Stabilization Club, National (Box 57., Folder 1-54)
    - American Legion (Folder 6-15)
    - Delta Sigma Rho (Folder 47)
    - Ignatius Donnelly Memorial Association (Folder 50)
    - F unsorted - Minnesota State Society of Washington (Box 58., Folder 1-58)
    - Farmer Labor Association (Folder 7)
    - Farmer Labor Party Clubs (Folder 8-10)
    - La Follette, Philip F. Speeches on the subject of a third party (Folder 50)
    - Lundeen, Ernest (Folder 53)
    - Minnesota Youth Assembly - Regulated Motor Transportation Association (Box 59., Folder 1-32)
    - Resolutions - United Spanish War Veterans (Box 60., Folder 1-23)
    - V unsorted - Youth Conference, Hennepin County (Box 61., Folder 1-17)
  - 1922-1935. Constituent mail unsorted within each letter of the alphabet
    - A - M (Box 62., Folder 1-13)
    - N - Z (Box 63., Folder 1-12)
  - 1932-1940. A chronological continuation of the previous series
    - A - C (Box 64., Folder 1-5)
    - D - H (Box 65., Folder 1-5)
    - H - Lundeen (Box 66., Folder 1-6)
    - Lundeen - O (Box 67., Folder 1-6)
    - P - S (Box 68., Folder 1-4)
    - S - Z (Box 69., Folder 1-6)
  - 1933, 1936. Corneaby, Edward (Box 70., Folder 1-2)
  - 1935-1939. Correspondence and reference file of federal and state agencies with names, addresses, telephone numbers and agency information. Filed alphabetically by name of agency
    - Administration and Finance - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 71., Folder 1-41)
    - Justice, Department of - Works Progress Administration (Box 72., Folder 1-71)
  - 1899-1925. Mostly constituent mail; some correspondence with clients and friends, arranged alphabetically
    - A unsorted (Box 73., Folder 1)
    - Abraham, R. H. (Folder 2)
    - Adams, R. H. (Folder 3)
    - Allbright, Charles S. (Folder 4)
    - Allen, G. W. (Folder 5)
    - Allen, Henry J. (Folder 6)
    - Allen & Fletcher (Folder 7)
    - Allin, C. D., Mrs. (Folder 8)
    - American Legion (Folder 9)
    - Anderson (unsorted) (Folder 10)
    - John Anderson Publishing Company (Folder 11)
    - Anderson, A. E. (Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Alfred (Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Clarence A. (Folder 14)
    - Anderson, Lewis (Folder 15)
    - Anderson, Otto E. (Folder 16)
    - Anderson, S. (Folder 17)
    - Anderson, Sydney (Folder 18)
    - Anderson, W. A. (Folder 19)
    - Andrews, John M. (Folder 20)
    - Andrews, V. L. (Folder 21)
    - Andrist, Charles M. (Folder 22)
    - Argus Publishing Company (Folder 23)
    - Arneson, Oscar (Folder 24)
    - Authier, George F. (Folder 25)
    - B unsorted (Folder 26)
    - B unsorted (Box 74., Folder 1)
    - Ba unsorted (Folder 2)
    - Baer, Ben (Folder 3)
    - Baer, John (Folder 4)
    - Baier, Florence C. (Folder 5)
    - Baldwin, Mathias (Folder 6)
    - Bales, Ernest N. (Folder 7)
    - Bank statements (Folder 8)
    - Bayer, Anthony M. (Folder 9)
    - Be unsorted (Folder 10)
    - Bean, Anna (Folder 11)
    - Beaulieu, Gus H. (Folder 12)
    - Beck, C. H. (Folder 13)
    - Bellemare, Edmund, Mrs. (Folder 14)
    - Bennett, James R. (Folder 15)
    - Bentall, J. O. (Folder 16)
    - Beresford State Bank (Folder 17)
    - Berg, Herman (Folder 18)
    - Berg, John (Folder 19)
    - Bergquist, John (Folder 20)
    - Berquist, Amelia (Folder 21)
    - Bertelson Brothers (Folder 22)
    - Bi unsorted (Folder 23)
    - Bibb, C. W. (Folder 24)
    - Bill, Eugene S. (Folder 25)
    - Bissell, F. S. (Folder 26)
    - Bjork, Abe (Folder 27)
    - Blake, O. H. (Folder 28)
    - Blakey, Roy G. (Folder 29)
    - Board of Education, Minneapolis (Folder 30)
    - Bohne, L. F. (Folder 31)
    - Bond Camp (Folder 32)
    - Boteler, William C. (Box 75., Folder 1)
    - Boutell Brothers (Folder 2)
    - Boutwell, Edwin (Folder 3)
    - Bowler, B. H. (Folder 4)
    - Bowler, S. A. (Folder 5)
    - Bowser, S. F. (Folder 6)
    - Bracken, H. M. (Folder 7)
    - Braden, Charles E. (Folder 8)
    - Brevick, H. K. (Folder 9)
    - Brisbane, Arthur (Folder 10)
    - Buell, C. J. (Folder 11)
    - Burnquist, J. A. A. (Folder 12)
    - C unsorted (Folder 13-14)
    - Calderwood, W. G. (Folder 15)
    - Campbell, William A. (Folder 16)
    - Carlson, Otto and Tillie Lundeen (Folder 17)
    - Carlson, Phillip E. (Folder 18)
    - Carr, Sam Houston (Folder 19)
    - Carroll, Dorr H. (Folder 20)
    - Cary, Herbert (Folder 21)
    - Castner, Frank H. and Theron S. (Folder 22)
    - Caswell, I. A. (Folder 23)
    - Chalgren, Edward A. (Box 76., Folder 1)
    - Chamberlain, George A. (Folder 2)
    - Champeau, Laura (Folder 3)
    - Chandler, S. E. (Folder 4)
    - Chaney, Lucian W. (Folder 5)
    - Chapman, Cecil B. (Folder 6)
    - Chapman, William A. (Folder 7)
    - Charles City, Iowa (Folder 8)
    - Christianson, Fred (Folder 9)
    - Christofk, Frank (Folder 10)
    - Church, Henry I. (Folder 11)
    - Civil Service Reform League (Folder 12)
    - Clark, Champ (Folder 13)
    - Clifford, Dan E. (Folder 14)
    - Coal situation (Folder 15)
    - Coast Guard (Folder 16)
    - Coffin, Ed (Folder 17)
    - Cole, Bert (Folder 18)
    - Colored People, National Association for Advancement of (Folder 19)
    - Congress, Library of (Folder 20)
    - Congressional Club (Folder 21)
    - Conklin Zonne Company (Folder 22)
    - Conscription repeal (Folder 23)
    - Cooper, E. V. (Folder 24)
    - Cowden, E. R. (Folder 25)
    - Cramer, R. D. (Folder 26)
    - Crane, A. A. (Folder 27)
    - Crosby, John (Folder 28)
    - Crume, George P. (Folder 29)
    - Cummins, Albert B. (Folder 30)
    - Curtis, Alfred (Folder 31)
    - D unsorted (Folder 32-33)
    - Dahl, John H. (Box 77., Folder 1)
    - Danielson, Anna (Folder 2)
    - Darcy, Hugh P. (Folder 3)
    - F. A. Davis Company (Folder 4)
    - Davis, Glen H. (Folder 5)
    - Dean and Helgerson (Folder 6)
    - Deane, E. L. (Folder 7)
    - Dehnel, Paul (Folder 8)
    - Deming, W. E. J. (Folder 9)
    - Devold, A. O. (Folder 10)
    - Dibble, Karl A. (Folder 11)
    - Dietrichson, Mary (Folder 12)
    - Doering, Bertha C. (Folder 13)
    - Doland, D. P. (Folder 14)
    - Donaher, Josephine (Folder 15)
    - Dresser, Alfred (Folder 16)
    - Duncan, George F. (Folder 17)
    - Duquette, Adrian, Mrs. (Folder 18)
    - E unsorted (Folder 19)
    - Eberhart, Adolph O. (Folder 20)
    - Eckelberry, Goldie (Folder 21)
    - Edlund, Carl (Folder 22)
    - Edwards, Albert E. (Folder 23)
    - Ege, James H. (Folder 24)
    - Eitel, George (Folder 25)
    - Ekern, Herman L. (Folder 26)
    - 11th Ward Improvement Association (Folder 27)
    - Ellis, Bert (Folder 28)
    - Ellsworth, Franklin F. (Folder 29)
    - Engerud, Holt and Frame (Folder 30)
    - Engstad, J. E. (Folder 31)
    - Engstrom, A. P. (Folder 32)
    - Equitable Life Insurance Association (Folder 33)
    - Erickson, Agnes (Folder 34)
    - Erickson, Anton H. (Folder 35)
    - Erickson, Charles G. (Folder 36)
    - Erickson, E. H. (Folder 37)
    - Erickson, Henry M. (Folder 38)
    - Erickson, Nels (Folder 39)
    - Ericsson, Bernard C. (Folder 40)
    - Evans, E. T. (Folder 41)
    - Everington, James (Folder 42)
    - Evjen, John O. (Folder 43)
    - F unsorted (Box 78., Folder 1-2)
    - Farmer Labor candidates, 1920 (Folder 3)
    - Fewell, Harold M. (Folder 4)
    - Fisher, H. E. (Folder 5)
    - Fontaine, Paul B. (Folder 6)
    - Friel, John S. (Folder 7)
    - G unsorted (Folder 8-9)
    - Garland, Thomas M. (Folder 10)
    - Gibert, Charles W. (Folder 11)
    - Gilman, E. Dow (Folder 12)
    - Goltz, Ernest (Folder 13)
    - Goodwin, Harry (Folder 14)
    - Gorman, John (Folder 15)
    - Gray, W. I. (Folder 16)
    - Gustafson, Karl (Folder 17)
    - H unsorted (Box 79., Folder 1-4)
    - Haines, Lynn (Folder 5)
    - Halbert, Hubert T. (Folder 6)